# **ARTIOM CATRUC**

+40724609023

Java Developer

artiom.catruc@yahoo.com



Bucharest, Plaza Residence



# **SUMMARY**

An ambitious, industrious and greedy for knowledge and experience young-future specialist. Willing to learn and achieve new skills needed for the job, searching for a Software Developer position where I can improve my personal abilities and contribute to the growth of organization.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **University Maritime of Constanta**

Bachelor in engineering an Management in transport 2018-2022

## SKILLS

- Programming Languages:
  - o Java, JavaScript, Pyton
- Tools
  - Linux, Spring Boot, Spring Boot, Hibernate, Java Core, Maven, Rest-Api, SpringData, MySQL, React, Git
- Soft skills:
  - Teamwork, analytical / problemsolving, Communication
- Foreign Languages:
  - o English (B1), Russian (C2)

## CERTIFICATIONS

Udemy course: Diploma java developer 2023-2024

Avantaj consult: Diploma front-end developer 2022-2023

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### INTERNSHIP AT STEFANINI MOLDOVA SRL

Frontend Developer | 2023-2024

- Experience with UI libraries, including Material-UI (MUI), styled-components, CSS, and SCSS/SASS.
- Strong understanding of OOP.
- Command Line, Disk Systems, Networking, Operational Systems
- Skilled in working with API requests, utilizing Axios and RTK Ouerv
- Good understanding of MySQL
- Version Control: Git, GitHub

#### **Assistant Manger**

Sushi Terra | 2021-2023

- Drove sales and controlled costs to support revenue and profitability targets.
- Optimised employee schedules by balancing company priorities with staff leave requests and shift preferences.
- Helped senior management plan and carry out daily operations and meet key objectives.
- Implemented staffing strategies to secure qualified personnel to meet business demands.

## **PROJECTS**

## ClubMember | Java

**Technologies**: Java for the backend logic and application development, CSV file for data storage and retrieval. <a href="https://github.com/artiomcatruc/ClubMemberJava">https://github.com/artiomcatruc/ClubMemberJava</a>

#### Todos | JavaScript

**Technologies**: React, HTML, CSS, JSX, REST API Integration, BootsTrap 5, React Router, Context API, Component, <a href="https://github.com/artiomcatruc/todos">https://github.com/artiomcatruc/todos</a>